MAXIMILIAN ROZANO

BOSTON, MA (908) 244-7450 ROZANOMAX@GMAIL.COM LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY

Software enthusiast with full stack development skills and strong fundamentals in quality assurance. Able to perform in a fast-paced agile environment with experience in planning, executing, and reporting results of test cases across multiple teams. Able to build and meet feature requirements and spin up web servers from scratch.

SKILLS

Tools: Jira, Git, Postman, MongoDB, SQL, Jenkins, DataDog, Selenium Webdriver, LaunchDarkly, Sparkpost, Cl/CD **Programming**: JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Python, Java, SQL, Flask, Airflow, Docker, Unix, AWS (Elastic, SQS), HTML. CSS

EXPERIENCE

Reggora, Boston — Software QA Engineer

FEBRUARY 2021 - MAY 2022

- Developed frontend platform features in React.js affecting 50,000+ daily users.
- Spearheaded UI/UX initiative with Tech Lead and Product Designer to revamp Appraiser platform.
- Tested new features and fixes locally, in development, staging, and production across multiple teams.
- Devised and executed 100+ cohesive, detailed manual test plans for new features being developed across web and mobile platforms.
- Verified and manipulated data using MongoDB for certain test scenarios.
- Rebuilt/deployed environments using GitLab/Jenkins.
- Authored MRs for bug fixes/hash updates for web platforms' frontend repositories.
- Collaborated with developers to resolve technical issues that arose from features/fixes.
- Cooperated with Product Manager to strategize how to implement new features according to customer desires.

TCM, Boston — Mobile App Developer

SEPTEMBER 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

- Developed mobile application using Android Studio to cater to individuals intending to use Traditional Chinese Medicine's tongue diagnosis via mobile camera.
- Worked closely with partner and professor to ensure application could recognize tongues using PyTorch and convolutional neural networks.

Dolume, **Boston** — *Technology Consultant Intern*

JANUARY 2019 - APRIL 2019

- Oversaw dozens of employee tickets with Spiceworks, communicated between multiple partners for network management, and created thin clients for employee usage.
- Developed a communication network to replace pagers to improve contact.
- Maintained clients' servers and access points.

EDUCATION

Wentworth Institute of Technology, Boston

SEPTEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2020

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics

PROJECTS

TCM Tongunosis | Owner

Used Java (Android) for frontend, Python for backend, and PyTorch/Torchvision for ML (CNN).

TEDxMCPHS Website | Owner | Website

- Developed TEDxMCPHS' website from scratch using React.js, Redux, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.
- Managed inquiries for their speaker events that sold over 350 tickets.

Headcount Application for Boston Code Camp | Lead Developer

- Developed desktop and mobile applications using JavaFX, React Native, and SQLite for users to measure engagement throughout speakers' sessions at Boston Code Camp.
- Lead front-end development of desktop application and delegated tasks among the team.
- Held regularly scheduled meetings based on Agile software development approach.